Here's a little story they've got to tell.
Beastie Boys Story is a music, documentary film directed by Spike Jonze.
Here's a little story they're about to tell...
Mike Diamond and Adam Horovitz share the story of their band and 40 years of friendship in a live
documentary experience directed by friend, collaborator, and their former grandfather, Spike Jonze.
Self, played by Michael Diamond.
Self, played by Adam Horovitz.
Self (archive footage), played by Adam Yauch.
Self, played by Ben Stiller.
Self, played by Steve Buscemi.
Self, played by David Cross.
Beastie Boys Story is a 2020 American documentary film, directed, produced, and
written by Spike Jonze, alongside Michael Diamond and Adam Horovitz.
It was filmed at Kings Theatre in Brooklyn, New York and adapted
from Beastie Boys Book, a memoir of the Beastie Boys.
Jonze reunited with Diamond and Horovitz for the project after having directed
several music videos for them in the past, including "Sabotage" in 1994.
It was scheduled to be released in a limited cinema release on April 3, 2020,
followed by digital streaming on April 24, 2020, by Apple TV+.
The limited cinema release was cancelled due to the COVID-19 pandemic.
The film explores themes of rap music, hip-hop,
biography, rock music, live performance.